抱歉  他吵醒你了
Sorry he woke you.
不是他
Oh, it wasn't him.
那是我又打呼嚕了
Was I snoring again?
我還以為那聲音是低空噴氣機
I thought it was a low-flying jet.
謝謝你能陪他玩
Thanks for playing with him.
沒什么的
I don't mind.
反正我也需要早起
I had to get up early anyway
還得開車回家換衣服上班呢
to drive home and get changed for work.
他是個乖孩子
He's a good kid.
我很想去你那里
You know, I'd like to stay at your place,
但是我有本杰明要照顧  所以
but when I have Benjamin, it's...
我知道  沒關系
I know. It's fine.
你得小心了  女士
You know, you should be careful, lady.
我指不定什么時候就娶了你
I could still make an honest woman of you yet.
你可以的
You actually could.
你聽說上個月的政策變化了嗎
Did you hear about last month's policy change?
聽說了  不再限制辦公室戀情
Oh, yeah. No more sanctions on office relationships.
我讀了郵件
Yeah. Read the e-mail.
對啊  只要他們之間不存在等級問題
Right. As long as there's no rank issues.
也就是說  我沒法和里斯本約會了
Right. So, I, uh... I couldn't date Lisbon.
沒錯  你想約里斯本嗎
Right. But do you want to date Lisbon?
不想  老天  我不是
No. God, no. I just--
不
No.
他們還允許探員之間結婚呢
They're even letting agents get married.
太好了
Awesome.
你要先去洗澡嗎
You want to shower first?
你去吧
Oh... you go.
好的
All right.
里斯本  太好了
Lisbon. Good.
咱們去納帕  你來開車
We're going to Napa. You drive.
兇殺案報道
Homicide bulletins?
熱點新聞
Hot off the press.
鴨塘里有具無名尸體在等著呢
A John Doe in a duck pond awaits.
聽起來應該歸當地警方管轄
Well, that sounds like a case for local authorities.
答對了
Bingo.
納帕啊  等一下
Napa. Okay, wait a minute.
那是麥卡利斯特警長的管轄區
That's Sheriff McAllister's jurisdiction
你想去調查血腥約翰嫌疑人
You want to go and investigate a Red John suspect.
調查是你的事
Investigating is your thing.
我只是想去多了解一下他
I'd just like to get to know him a little better.
走嗎
Shall we?
加利福尼亞  納帕谷
加州  納帕谷  貝拉維斯塔教堂
園丁發現尸體沉在池塘底下
Gardening crew found the body submerged in the pond.
看起來他泡水里還沒幾個小時
Doesn't look like he was in the water for more than a few hours.
頭骨后方有重擊傷痕
There's a contusion on the back of the skull.
可能是被人從背后偷襲
I'm guessing someone caught him from behind.
他在深更半夜的
What was he doing behind a church
在教堂后面干什么
in the middle of the night?
個人物品呢
Any personal belongings?
沒有發現錢包和手機
No wallet or cell phone.
只有前兜里有些錢
Just a money roll in his front pocket.
32塊零鈔
$32 in small bills.
簡
Hey, Jane?
有什么想法嗎
Care to offer your opinion?
這些鴨子很喜歡吃松餅
These ducks love muffins.
你幫了"大忙"了
Very helpful.
看他們游了
Look at 'em go!
游騎兵們來了啊
I see the cavalry has arrived.
麥卡利斯特警長
Sheriff McAllister.
里斯本探員  什么風
Agent Lisbon. What, uh...
什么風把您這精英小組吹到我們這小地方來了
What brings your crack team to our little slice of heaven?
你知道的  就找個借口來見識下葡萄酒鄉
Oh, you know, any excuse to get up to Wine Country.
指北加州種植葡萄的地區
好吧  我們很歡迎有人來幫忙
Well, we always welcome the help,
但是我認為我可以處理好這件事
but I expect I can handle this one.
實際上
Well, to be honest, it was uh
是我想要來的
It was me that wanted to come out here.
-是這樣啊  -我有個感覺
- Is that a fact? - Well, more of a feeling.
這里的事件不那么簡單
I think there's more out here than meets the eye.
怎么說
How so?
-你沒感覺到  -沒有
- You don't feel it? - no.
你有什么發現
What's your take?
發現什么
On what?
死者的事
Our friend.
我們來看看吧
Well, let's have a look.
1 5 6
"One five six."
他會不會是推銷員  這是他的代碼
You suppose he's repping his code?
1-5-6是電話銷售人員用的地區代碼
Area code 1-5-6 is reserved for telemarketers,
所以應該不是
so I'm guessing no.
他看起來是那種工作懈怠的人
Well... he's kind of a slack-looking fella.
光看尸體都覺得他前途無望
Gloomy, even for a corpse.
廉價的服飾  也沒啥肌肉
You know, cheap clothes, no muscle tone.
低收入的辦公室白領
Sedentary low-income job.
應該是這樣
Sounds right.
該你了
Your turn.
鞋底紋理集中在腳跟部
The tread on his shoes wrap up around the heel
為了防止腳跟打滑
to prevent the heel from slipping,
與很多賽車手一樣
Like those of a serious race car driver,
或者是一個假裝會賽車的快遞員
Or a delivery man that likes to pretend he races cars.
如此這般  加上他兜里
Couple that with the roll of small bills
找到的零錢
found in his pant pocket...
披薩送貨員
Pizza delivery man.
也可能是送墨西哥菜或肋排的
Could be Mexican. Or ribs.
可能
Could be.
但是  你沒聞到
But, uh... you don't detect
他身上有股淡淡的牛至味道嗎
the faint scent of oregano about him?
這是個大線索
That's a leap.
■
人人影視
YYeTs.com
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com
■
翻譯：丁  面條打包子  王小麥  Michael  壹不貳  那時花開
超感警探
第六季
第三集
■
時間軸：兜兜兜爹  Sagelibra   校對：灰灰是菇涼  狂舞之鶴
第六季
第三集
■
特效&后期：灰灰是菇涼   精校&總監：灰灰是菇涼
有什么想法
What do you think?
他沒有看上去的那么笨
Well, he's not as dumb as he looks.
他是血腥約翰嗎
Well, is he Red John?
有點言之過早
It's too early to say.
我們要怎么查啊
How do we find out?
我需要和他單獨在一起
I need to be alone with him.
這可不太明智
Well, that would not be wise.
在搞什么呢
What's cookin' in here?
找到什么線索了嗎
Spot any clues?
沒有
No.
不過你看到那個錘子沒有
Well, just that hammer up there. You see it?
它錘頭上沾的是不是血跡
Is that blood on the hitting side?
可能是的
Could be.
我叫人來取證
I'll call forensics.
伙計們
Fellows?
你看到了嗎
Did you see that?
他不想去爬梯子
He did not want to go up that ladder.
那個心理醫生不是說過
Didn't the psychiatrist's office say
血腥約翰怕高嗎
that Red John was afraid of heights?
很機智啊  里斯本
That's very astute, Lisbon.
火眼金睛
Well observed.
他們搞完外邊的事就會過來
They'll join us when they're done outside.
我等不了那么長
Yeah, I can't wait that long.
警長  你能爬梯子上去拿一下嗎
Sheriff, would you mind going up the ladder for me?
你想讓我穿著這種尖頭靴子
You want me to climb all the way up there
去爬那么高的梯子嗎
in these pointed toe boots?
沒合適的鞋子可不行
That's a job for sensible shoes.
最好能幫我這個大忙
It would be a big help.
我來吧  頭兒
I got it, boss.
謝謝你  孩子
Thank you, son.
老大  周在車管所的系統里找到了死者的指紋
Hey, boss, Cho got a D.M.V. hit on the victim's prints.
他叫拉里·金凱德
His name is Larry Kincaid,
46歲  無犯罪記錄
46, clean record.
看起來不是血  應該是油漆
No. Doesn't look like blood. I think it's paint.
謝了  瑞斯比
Thanks, Rigsby.
金凱德住在瓦卡維爾市
Kincaid lived in Vacaville and worked
職業是一名披薩送貨司機
as a pizza delivery driver.
受害人在納帕做什么
What was the victim doing in Napa?
他的老板說他是來參加他侄女今晚的婚禮的
His boss said he was here for his niece's wedding tonight.
史黛絲·邦納
Stacey Bonner.
晚宴彩排昨晚在這里舉辦的
The rehearsal dinner was here last night.
好吧  你倆待在這邊
All right, you two stay in the area
找找目擊證人
and look for witnesses.
我們去那婚禮派對看看
We've got a wedding party to find.
加利福尼亞  納帕  七仙女酒廠
用桌子來幫你搖晃紅酒  桌子是你朋友
Use the table to help you swirl. The table's your friend.
你這動作真性感
You look so sexy when you do that.
這樣做能將氧氣帶入紅酒中
This draws oxygen into the wine
散發出酒的芳香
to bring out the aroma.
誰在乎它聞起來什么樣  喝吧
Who cares what it smells like? Let's drink.
打擾一下  這是邦納和薩拉斯的婚宴嗎
Excuse me. Uh, uh, is this the Bonner-Salas wedding party?
我是史黛西·邦納  有什么事嗎
I'm Stacey Bonner. Can I help you?
我是加調局的特蕾莎·里斯本探員
Yes, I'm Agent Teresa Lisbon with the CBI.
這位是派翠克·簡
This is Patrick Jane.
今早我們在貝拉維斯塔婚禮教堂后面
We found a body behind the Bella Vista Wedding Chapel
發現了一具尸體
this morning.
是出席你婚宴的客人
It's a member of your party.
他叫做拉里·金凱德
His name is Larry Kincaid.
拉里舅舅  不要啊
Uncle Larry? Oh, no.
沒一個人掉眼淚啊
Don't everyone cry at once.
邀請我妻子的弟弟只是出于禮貌
My wife's brother was something of a courtesy invite.
他是個好人  但是
He's a nice enough guy, but...
不太通人情世故
a little off, socially speaking.
好吧
Okay.
我想你是新娘的父親
Uh, you're the bride's father, I take it.
那你的妻子在哪
And, uh, where's your wife?
她回酒店休息了
She's resting back at the hotel.
她昨晚開始犯偏頭痛
She came down with a migraine last night.
可憐的拉里舅舅  媽媽一定會崩潰的
Poor uncle Larry. Mom's gonna freak out.
沒事的  親愛的
It's okay, carino.
婚禮被毀了
The wedding is ruined!
他是怎么死的
What happened to him?
我們正想要查明這一點
That's what we're trying to find out.
我能看下尸體嗎
Can I see the body?
蘇西  你這樣不太合適
Suzie, that's not very appropriate.
這就是生活啊
This is life happening.
我們不能消極躲避
We can't shut our eyes.
那  我能看看他嗎
So... can I look at him?
不行
No.
在死者生前  誰最后一個見過他
Who was the last person who saw the victim alive?
我們所有人  在彩排晚宴后
All of us. After the rehearsal dinner,
我們都想去大的派對帳篷
we all hit up the big party tent.
那叫婚禮禮篷
The wedding pavilion.
是婚禮禮篷
The wedding pavillion.
就是教堂旁邊那個大帳篷
It's the big tent by the chapel.
當時酒喝完了  拉里主動提出去拿酒
We ran out of wine, and Larry offered to make an alcohol run.
我是薩拉斯先生  羅伯托是我兒子
I'm Mr. Salas. Roberto's my son.
后來拉里舅舅回來過嗎
Did uncle Larry ever come back?
沒有  但我們也沒覺得奇怪
No. But we weren't surprised.
還以為他是想找個借口離開派對
It felt like he was looking for an excuse to leave the party.
沒錯  就好像他
Yeah. It's like he was...
在做鬼之前已經像鬼一樣游蕩了
a ghost before he was a ghost.
安格爾  你個蠢貨
Angel, you're such an idiot.
他可是她舅舅
He was her uncle.
很抱歉  親愛的  他看起來人還不錯
I'm sorry, baby. He seemed like an okay guy.
我不是為了拉里舅舅哭的
I'm not crying about uncle Larry.
是為了婚禮的事
It is the wedding day.
我們還是會結婚的  對吧  對吧
Hey, we're still gonna get married, right? Right?
也許吧  但一切都太令人沮喪了
I guess. But it's all so... sordid.
好啦
Yeah.
里斯本說這是死者生前
Lisbon said this was the last room
最后待過的屋子
the victim was seen alive in.
這將會是場很美的婚禮
Well, it's gonna be a beautiful wedding.
想要花錢  我能想出更好的方法
Eh, I can think of better ways to spend good money.
是嗎  比如說呢  新的皮組合沙發嗎
Oh, yeah? Like what? A new leather sectional?
不是
No.
好吧  你怎么猜到的
Okay, how'd you guess?
我以前一直夢想著能有個灰姑娘一樣的婚禮
I used to dream about having a Cinderella wedding.
真的嗎  你從沒提過
You did? You never said anything.
很久以前的事了
Ah. It was a long time ago.
現在聽起來肯定挺傻的
I suppose it all seems silly now.
我們是警察
Police.
誰在里面
Who's in here?
慢慢走出來
Step out slowly.
別開槍
Don't shoot.
把它放下
Set it down.
把手背到身后
Hands behind your back.
不是你們想的那樣
It's not what you think.
這是什么
What's this?
在結婚蛋糕里加瀉藥嗎
Laxatives in the wedding cake, huh?
-真是為人著想啊  -你叫什么名字
- That's a cute move. - What's your name?
奧斯卡·薩拉斯
Oscar Salas.
新郎的弟弟
The groom's brother.
你為什么想要破壞你哥哥的婚禮  奧斯卡
Why'd you want to ruin your brother's wedding, Oscar?
為什么不呢
Why not?
你不喜歡他的未婚妻嗎
You don't like his fiancee?
她是個刷推狂  超級自戀狂
Twitter freak. Completely self-obsessed.
他們都是  像每時每刻都需要別人關注的小孩
They all are. Children who need constant feedback.
等他們吃了那個蛋糕
Just wait until they try that cake.
我真是等不及要看他們的推特了
I am dying to read that tweet.
拉里舅舅人怎么樣
What about uncle Larry?
他看起來不錯
He seems cool.
至少他跟別人不一樣
At least he doesn't follow the pack.
你知道昨晚在彩排晚宴之后
Did you know he was murdered last night
他被謀殺了嗎
after the rehearsal dinner?
不知道
No.
你知道誰有可能想傷害他嗎
Any idea who might want to hurt him?
有  安格爾
Yeah. Angel.
我哥哥的伴郎
My brother's best man.
他一直在不停說拉里的壞話
He talked trash about Larry all the time.
他好像還給拉里發過短信
I think he sent him text messages, too.
你對死者有什么不滿
What was your beef with the victim?
沒有不滿
No beef.
我們聽說你不喜歡他
We heard you didn't like him.
你們聽錯了
You heard wrong.
我對他一點想法都沒有
I didn't have no opinion of him.
跟他不怎么熟
Barely knew the guy.
我們還聽說你通過短信刁難過他
We also heard you harassed him with text messages.
那不是真的
That's not true.
不如你把短信讓我看一下吧
How about you show me those texts?
我不會把手機給你的
I'm not giving you my phone.
我在半小時內就能搞到法院指令
I can have a court order here in 30 minutes.
只不過那時  我將視你為嫌犯
Only then, I'll be looking at you as a suspect.
"拉里  你老板那邊有消息了嗎
"Hey, Larry, any word yet from your boss?
我真的很需要那份工作  謝了  伙計"
I could really use the work. Thanks, buddy."
他在幫你找一份披薩店的工作嗎
He was helping you get a pizza job?
我需要工作  那又怎樣
I need work. So what?
-你得到那份工作了嗎  -沒有
- You get the job? - Nope.
在彩排宴會之后的派對期間
Did you leave the wedding tent at any point
你離開過婚禮帳篷嗎
during the after party?
沒有  我一直待到結束
No, I was there till the end.
不信你去問別人
Ask anyone.
在我離開的時候  拉里早都沒影了
And Larry was long gone by the time I left.
多謝你前來  邦納夫人
Thank you for coming, Mrs. Bonner.
你有沒有看到你弟弟離開派對
Did you happen to see your brother leave the party?
沒有  我當時頭疼
No, I, uh... I had a headache.
我就提前離開了派對
I left the party early
走回了蜜月套房
and walked back to the honeymoon suite.
為什么你住在蜜月套房里
Why were you in the honeymoon suite?
這個婚禮的錢都是我們付的
We're paying for this wedding.
死者在派對上都做了些什么
What was the victim doing at the party?
沒什么特別的
The usual.
站著  在一旁看
Standing... watching.
說實話  我覺得他還挺可憐的
To be honest, I felt sorry for the man.
你和死者是什么關系
What was your relationship with the victim?
拉里是我未婚妻的舅舅
Larry's my fiancee's uncle,
所以在我看來  他就是我的親人
so as far as I'm concerned, he's my blood.
但這個親人很古怪
But weird blood, you know?
你知道有什么人想要傷害死者嗎
Do you know of anybody who may have wanted to harm the victim?
沒有人跟他很親  但也沒人跟他交惡
Nobody really felt strongly enough about him
都挺平淡的
one way or the other.
他就好像  跟大家都不親
He just kinda... floated along
游離于家族之外
like family flotsam.
他有那種能力
That was his strength, you know?
那種在社交中不引人注目的能力
The power of social invisibility.
我想我可能會愛上他
I think I could have loved him.
在派對上他跟什么人說話了嗎
Did he talk to anyone at the party?
對  我兒子在大學認識的朋友  查理
Yes. My son's friend Charlie from college.
你知道羅伯托上過大學嗎
Did you know Roberto went to college?
我們家里頭一個
First in the family.
我那時已經喝高了
Well, I was pretty toasted.
我記得拉里那時在談論一把新步槍
But I think Larry was talking about a new rifle.
他說他買來自衛的
Said he bought it to defend himself.
步槍  你確定嗎
Rifle? Are you sure?
死者沒有槍支所有記錄
The victim doesn't have any record of gun ownership.
我覺得他只是想要融入圈子
I think he was just trying to fit in.
想成為一分子才這么說的
You know, be one of the guys.
所以他才會主動提出去給我們買酒
Same reason Larry offered to go on a liquor run for us.
你有看到死者離開派對嗎
Did you see the victim leave the party?
我不會說英語[西語]
No hablo inglés.
稍等一下
Excuse me.
婚禮上一定有人看到了什么
Somebody in that wedding party had to have seen something.
空氣中充滿了愛意  里斯本
Love is in the air, Lisbon.
這兩家人就要聯姻了
These two families are about to be married.
不推他們一把他們不會出賣對方的
They're not gonna turn on each other without a push.
怎么推
What kind of push?
要查出誰殺了拉里舅舅
If we want to learn who killed uncle Larry,
我們要做到以正視聽
then we need to clear the air.
也就是說不要再為了新人裝友善了
That means no more playing nice for the happy couple.
你們要誠實
We need some honesty.
-誰不誠實了  -首先是你
- Who's not being honest? - Well, you, for starters.
你應該是新郎的姐姐吧
You're the groom's sister, I take it.
也是我的伴娘
And my bridesmaid.
這么做本來挺好的
Yes, that was a lovely gesture,
但是這樣反而會讓她尷尬
but you put her in a very awkward position,
-因為她討厭你  -我沒有
- because she resents you. - No, I don't.
你有  誠實點
Yes, you do. Be honest.
你討厭我嗎  羅絲
Do you resent me, Rose?
你對我弟弟頤指氣使  總是指正他
You talk down to my brother! You're always correcting him.
那不是真的  她什么時候
That's not true. When has she ever--
別說話  羅伯托
Not now, Roberto.
羅絲  你生氣是因為
Rose, are you mad at me
我幫你付了伴娘禮服的錢嗎
because I paid for your bridesmaid dress?
你可沒付我的禮服的錢
You didn't pay for my dress.
你又不是售貨員
You don't work in retail.
現在她對我這么做了
Now she's doing it to me.
史黛西學的是英語專業  丫頭
Stacey was an English Major, Chica.
她只是講起話來有點高傲而已
She just sounds superior.
"丫頭"  我女兒可不是你家里的傭人
"Chica"? My daughter is not your housemaid.
她會說英語
Hey. She speaks English.
你們能不能互相尊重一下彼此
Can we all show some respect here, please?
我們是一家人了
We're a family now.
是啊  幸福的一大家子
Yes, one big, happy family.
所以你才在彩排后的派對上和新娘的媽媽
Is that why you hooked up with the bride's mother
勾搭到一起是嗎
at the after party?
你說什么
What was that?
你說你妻子昨晚偏頭痛
You said that your wife had a migraine last night,
說大概是喝多了
which is the enablers' code for "Drunk."
而今天  她都不敢直視新郎的爸爸
And today, she can't look the groom's father in the eye.
所以今天早上她才沒去品酒
That's why she wasn't at the wine tasting this morning.
你居然對我媽下手
You made a move on my mom?
你怪我爸干什么  也許是你媽才是奸夫
Why are you blaming papi? Maybe your mom's the adulterer.
-是奸婦  -別糾正他了
- Adultress. - Stop correcting him!
我現在發現了
Yeah! I see it now.
閉上你的嘴
Okay, shut up!
今天是我結婚  我想說什么做什么
This is my wedding day, and I will say and do
都是我說了算
whatever I want.
而我要
And what I want...
取消婚禮
is to cancel this wedding.
生活啊  充滿了意外
Life. Happening.
史黛西  你那是氣話
Stacey, you don't mean that.
你們為這場婚禮準備了幾個月了
You guys have been planning this for months.
我從佛羅里達飛過來參加你們的婚禮
I flew in from Florida to be here.
你自便吧
You're all on your own.
這招推得不錯
Nice push.
會有好進展的  你很快就能看到了
Ah, something good will come out of this. You'll see.
-可以回納帕了嗎  -請吧
- Can we go back to Napa now? - Please.
新郎的弟弟說
Groom's brother said
雙方家庭都不贊成他們結婚
that neither side of the family approves of the wedding,
但他們都裝作贊成
but they're both pretending like they do.
現在可不裝了
Not anymore.
我跟進了那條步槍的線索
I followed up on that rifle tip.
根據銀行記錄  拉里舅舅
According to bank records, uncle Larry wrote
兩周前用個人支票買了槍
a personal check for one two weeks ago.
我們需要槍支銷售商的聯系方式
We need contact information for the firearms dealer.
一個私人牧場主賣給他的
A private rancher sold it to him.
叫詹姆斯·哈里斯  我有他的地址
James Harris. I have an address.
死者說買槍是為了保護自己
The victim said he brought a rifle to protect himself.
我們查查看是為了防誰  瑞斯比  跟我走
Let's find out from who. Rigsby, you're with me.
我會對婚宴受邀名單上的人做背景核查
I'll run background checks on the invitation list.
我還以為你是來破案的
I thought you were supposed to solve a crime,
而不是破壞婚禮
not, uh, destroy a wedding.
那是兇手干的
Well, I'd say the killer did that.
我等著驚嘆你敏銳的洞察力了
I'm prepared to marvel at your insight.
誰是兇手
Who's the killer?
還在查
Still working on it.
是嗎  我這下真的吃驚了  我還以為
Really? I'm surprised. I'd have...
我還以為你現在應該已經抓住他了
I'd have thought you'd have him in cuffs by now.
抱歉讓你失望了
Oh, I hate to disappoint you.
簡  邦納夫人想和你談談
Jane. Mrs. Bonner would like to have a word with you.
你說得對
You were right.
我離開派對之前  和薩拉斯先生接吻了
Before I left the party, Mr. Salas and I shared a kiss.
一個喝多了以后錯誤的吻
A drunken, mistaken kiss.
你們是在哪里醉吻的
Uh, where did this, uh, inebriated smooch take place?
教堂后面
Behind the chapel.
你們有看見池塘邊有什么動靜嗎
Did you see anything here by the pond?
沒有  但是午夜前后我們有聽見水濺聲
No, but we heard a splash around midnight.
有聽到任何尖叫  或者掙扎的聲音嗎
Did you hear any... screams or sounds of a struggle?
我應該去幫他的
I should have gone to help him.
那也沒什么用
It wouldn't have mattered.
他是在其他地方被殺害的
It seems he was killed someplace else.
只是被拋尸在此而已
The body was just dumped here.
兇手把尸體藏在池塘里  等到婚禮結束
Hiding the body until after the wedding in the pond,
要我說  這池塘可不是藏尸體的好地方
which is not such a great hiding place, I would think.
太不隱蔽了
A little too public.
貝拉維斯塔
Bella Vista.
教堂名為音譯  實意后有解釋
貝拉維斯塔
Bella Vista.
意大利語美景的意思
"Beautiful view" in Italian.
這里的美景在哪兒
Where is this, uh, bella vista?
穿過樹林
Through the trees.
這才是拋尸的好地方
Now this is a place to dump a body.
好好看看
Take a look. Huh?
兇手把尸體拖到池塘邊
Killer hauls the body to the pond.
再多走幾步
Just a little bit further,
就可以把尸體拋在這里了
and he could have dumped it right here.
他說的對  那里什么都沒有
He's right. Nobody's finding anything down there.
過來伙計  來看看
Come over here, fella. Have a look.
不用了  我很熟悉那里的景色
No, I'm familiar with the view.
跟我們說說我們在看什么
Uh, tell us what we're looking at.
抱歉  我要回這個
Excuse me. I'm gonna take this.
第二次了
Strike two.
你現在相信我了嗎
You believe me now?
周  你覺得我適合結婚嗎
Hey, Cho, you think I'm a marrying type?
你跟孩子他媽求過婚了
You proposed to your baby mama.
是啊  因為每個孩子都應該有一對父母
Well, yeah, but every kid deserves two parents.
我是在說范佩爾
I was talking about Van Pelt.
-你把她肚子也搞大了嗎  -沒
- You knock her up, too? - No.
那為什么會說到這個
So why are we talking about this?
你一定沒看到局里的內部通知
Well, you clearly missed the departmental memo.
他們修改了辦公室戀情的規定
They changed the policy on office relationships.
不用再遮遮掩掩了
Don't have to lay low anymore.
那很好啊
Good for you.
如果我們想  我們甚至可以結婚
We could even get married if we wanted to.
哦
Ah.
就這樣嗎  "哦"
That's it? "Ah"?
她想結婚  可是你不想
She wants to get married and you don't want to.
才不是  也許是吧
No. Maybe.
不是  我不知道  你覺得我該怎么做
No. I don't know. What do you think I should do?
你想讓我來擔責任嗎
You want to make it my fault?
你說得對
Okay, you're right.
我該自己決定
It's my call.
你們是在私人土地上
You're on private property.
我們是加調局探員  你是詹姆斯·哈里斯嗎
CBI agents. You James Harris?
是的
That's right.
你大概兩周前賣了一把步槍給一個
You sell a rifle to a man named Larry Kincaid
叫拉里·金凱德的人嗎
about two weeks ago?
很有可能  我得查查收據
It's quite possible. I'd have to check my receipts.
你未經許可販賣槍支
It's a violation of state law
違反了本州的法律
for you to sell firearms without a license.
你的谷倉里藏著什么
What are you hiding in the barn?
我的私人軍火庫
My private arsenal.
請把門打開
Open the door, please.
把手放在我們能看到的地方
Keep your hands where we can see them.
如果我沒記錯
If I recall,
拉里買過一把這樣的槍
Larry bought one of these.
一把1840年產斯普林菲爾德步槍
A genuine 1840 springfield musket.
現在只能放空槍
It's rigged up to fire blanks now.
你是搞模擬內戰的
You're a Civil War re-enactor.
是的  納帕谷坎伯蘭郡警衛隊
That's right-- Field Commander
戰地指揮官
for the Napa Valley Cumberland Guard,
第156團的
156th Regiment.
我們下周在海角堡有一場戰役
We got a battle next week in Fort Point.
死者衣服上的156肯定是指這個
That must be what the "156" meant on the victim's shirt.
什么死者
What victim?
拉里昨晚被謀殺了
Larry was murdered last night
就在貝拉韋斯塔教堂后面
behind the Bella Vista Chapel.
很遺憾
Very sorry to hear that.
你知不知道有誰想傷害死者
You know of anyone who may have wanted to hurt the victim?
天啊  不知道  拉里人很好
Oh, God, no. No. Larry was a harmless sort.
不愛說話  但是個好兵
Quiet, but... a good soldier.
他的離去對我們這個小部隊來說
His loss is gonna leave a real whole
是個很大的損失
in our little community.
你弄壞了就得買
You break it, you buy it.
別理我  請別因為我停止祈禱
Oh, please, don't stop praying on my account.
我不是在祈禱
Oh, I'm not praying.
在教堂里  發短信
Texting. In church.
這不是罪過嗎
Isn't that a sin?
希望不是  我還靠這雙手吃飯呢
I hope not. I make my living with my thumbs.
很抱歉揭露了你妻子
I'm, uh, sorry for busting your wife.
這不是她第一次
It's not the first drunken kiss
酒后跟別的男人接吻了
she's shared with a man that wasn't me.
而且我也知道不會是最后一次
And I'm sure it won't be the last.
你知道誰殺了她弟弟嗎
Do you have any idea who killed her brother?
我想應該是婚禮上的人
I believe it was someone from the wedding party.
不  不  你錯了
No. No, you're wrong.
沒人會殺拉里
No one had any reason to kill uncle Larry.
就像沒人會殺  美洲駝一樣
It would be like... killing a llama.
為什么要殺它們呢
Why would you?
它們亂吐口水
They spit?
你是干什么的
What do you do for a living?
我是個投機商
I'm a speculator.
我搜尋價值被低估的資產
I look for undervalued assets.
哪類的
What kind of assets?
藝術品  島嶼
Oh, artworks, islands--
只要我能低買高賣就行
anything I can buy low and sell high.
上個月我在一個教堂拍賣會上
Last month I found a first edition
發現了頭版的《卡佛岱爾圣經》
Coverdale Bible at a church auction,
1535年史上第一個完全翻譯成現代英語的圣經版本
1535印刷的
printed in 1535.
本來打算在婚禮上朗讀上面的一段
I was gonna do a reading from it at the wedding.
值多少錢
How much is that worth?
五十萬吧
Oh, uh, half a million.
就買了一本古老的圣經
For an antique Bible.
它現在在哪
Where is it now?
在一家私人保安公司
With a private security firm.
他們會在今晚婚禮時送來
They were gonna deliver it here for the wedding tonight.
或許應該現在就賣掉它
Might as well just sell it now.
我是范佩爾探員
Agent Van Pelt.
格蕾斯  我需要你幫個忙
Grace, I need your help.
這對新人必須要按計劃
It is imperative that our young lovers
進行他們的婚禮
go ahead with the wedding as planned.
可能嗎  你毀了那個女孩的婚禮
Good luck with that. You ruined a girl's wedding.
是的  我沒法撫平他們心理的創傷
Yes, and I lack the putty to spackle those emotional wounds.
所以我才找你
That's why I'm calling you.
我有辦法
I have putty?
不  你有人生經驗
No, you have life experience.
用你的經驗說服新娘
Use it to convince the bride
她的"幸福人生"會從今晚開始
that her "happily ever after" begins tonight.
不是吧
Really?
簡對發生在候審室里的事
Jane is feeling really badly
感到十分抱歉
for what happened in the bull pen.
沒必要
He shouldn't.
我們走不到一塊  他還幫了我個大忙
This was never going to work. He did me a huge favor.
你的家人不想讓你們結婚
Your families don't want the marriage.
媽媽說羅伯托配不上我
Mom says I'm too smart for Roberto.
爸爸擔心他沒有能力照顧我
And my dad is worried he won't be able to take care of me.
而羅伯托的父母想讓他娶一個
And Roberto's parents just want him to marry
信天主教的女孩
a nice Catholic girl.
你想要什么
What do you want?
我想要羅伯托
I want Roberto.
但是
But...
太復雜了
it's too complicated.
所以你要放手了
So you're gonna throw it away?
聽我說
Look...
我也有想要一起度過下半輩子的人
I had someone I wanted to spend the rest of my life with.
但是  我們在一起意味著我要放棄工作
But... staying together would have ended my career.
所以我放手了
So I let him go.
怎么了
What happened?
我跟別人訂婚了
I got engaged to someone else.
結果卻很不好
That ended badly.
所以我開始封閉自己的內心
So I shut down a little inside.
這樣讓我感到更有安全感
Closed some doors to feel safer.
但是
But...
問題是  隨著時間流逝
the problem is with every passing year,
你關上的心門越來越多
you close more doors.
直到最后
Until eventually...
你都不知道會不會有人能走進你的心
you wonder if anyone will ever get inside again.
-太悲哀了  -是的
- That's really tragic. - Yeah.
所以我還留著那套裙子
Well, that's why I keep the dress.
你的婚紗
Your wedding dress?
我知道這很傻  是吧
I know. It's crazy, right?
但是
But...
它提醒著我  我以前是怎樣的
it reminds me of who I was...
天真  可能還有點傻  但是
Naive. Maybe a little foolish, but...
內心充滿希望
full of hope.
我擔心如果我扔掉婚紗
I'm afraid if I destroy that dress...
我就會忘記希望是什么滋味
I'll forget what hope feels like.
麥卡利斯特那邊怎么辦
What are we gonna do about McAllister?
除非我能跟他單獨相處一段時間
Well, until I get some alone time with him,
否則我得不出任何結論
I'm not gonna draw any conclusions.
他兩次都不想上高處
Well, he's avoided heights twice.
如果血腥約翰恐高
If Red John is acrophobic,
他為什么要告訴我的心理醫生
why would he tell my shrink?
為了獲得她的信任從而偷走她的文件
To gain her trust so he could steal her file--
殺她之前他也的確這么做了
which he did right before he killed her.
你們猜怎么著
Guess what?
我們要結婚了  沒有不愉快了
We're getting married. No hard feelings.
我覺得這個決定很好
Well, I think that's a great decision.
恭喜你們  當然
Congratulations. You-- of course, you know,
我們也得出席婚禮
we will have to attend the ceremony,
以防殺死拉里的兇手出現
just in case uncle Larry's killer reveals himself.
-好的  -你們應該跟著我們
- Okay. - Uh, you should follow us.
-法院關門了  -法院
- The courthouse closes. - Courthouse?
你們不是在納帕舉行婚禮嗎
What about your big Napa wedding?
是有點可惜  但是又能怎么樣呢
It's a waste, but, I mean, what can we do?
我找不到牧師  早上我叫他不用來的
I can't find a priest. I canceled him this morning.
而且教堂也只能再用兩個小時  所以
And we only have the chapel for two more hours. So...
知道嗎  其實我是一個
Well, you know, it turns out that I am, in fact,
有資質的婚禮司儀牧師
a certified wedding officiant.
-我可以給你們主婚  -我的天
- I can marry you. - Oh, my gosh.
-真是大救星啊  謝謝  -太感謝了
- You're a lifesaver. Thank you. - Thank you so much.
是我的榮幸
It would be my pleasure.
你才沒有資質呢
Oh, you are not legally ordained.
我有  只是從沒用上
Yeah, I've never used it.
我常覺得有一技傍身很方便
But I always thought it was a handy thing to have.
我才不信呢
I don't believe you.
我發誓  我一分鐘之內就能讓你結婚
I swear. I could marry you off in a minute.
嗨  羅恩
Hey, Ron.
別試探我
Don't tempt me.
我是麥卡利斯特警長
Sheriff McAllister.
我是派翠克·簡
Yeah, it's Patrick Jane.
有事嗎  派翠克
What can I do for you, Patrick?
我在教堂這邊  案子有突破了
Well, I'm at the chapel. We have a break in the case.
你多久能趕到這里見我
How soon can you meet me here?
非常快
Real soon.
真有趣  我在停車場看到你的車
Funny thing, I, uh, saw your car in the lot,
我剛好要來找你
and I was just coming to find you.
沒聽到你的腳步聲
I didn't hear you coming.
你走路很輕
You move quietly.
老習慣了
Well, it's an old habit.
我這大半輩子都在打獵
I've been a hunter most of my life.
真的嗎  你都打什么
Really? What do you hunt?
長臉的我都打
Anything with a face.
就是消遣嘛  對吧
Game is game, right?
-你打獵嗎  -我嗎  不打
- You hunt? - Me? No.
我有潔癖
No. Too squeamish. I--
我搞不了剝皮開肚那種事
I couldn't handle all the skinning and the gutting.
是啊
Yeah. Sure, yeah.
要收拾獵物把它大卸八塊
Clean and quarter a kill.
的確要有點膽量
It takes some stomach for that.
還得嗜血
And a certain bloodlust.
這話有點道理
There's a grain of truth in that.
鴨塘案有突破了是嗎
So you got a break in the duck pond killer case?
與其說突破不如說是計劃
Well... less a break, but, uh, more a plan.
我今晚要揭露兇手是誰
I'm gonna reveal the killer tonight.
我需要你和你的人
And I need you and your people
先放手別管了
to just hang back.
沒問題
No problem.
很感激你讓我的工作變得這么輕松
I truly appreciate you making my job easier for me.
你真美
You look great.
謝謝夸獎  韋恩
Thank you, Wayne.
簡覺得兇手會中途溜出宴會
Jane thinks our man's gonna try to sneak out of the reception.
我們要守在那  我會跟著他
We need to be there. I'm gonna follow him.
如果他太小心不敢行動怎么辦
What if he's too cautious to make a move while we're here?
如果他在婚宴這邊
If he's in the reception tent
待了超過兩小時
for more than two hours,
簡希望你們能弄點小插曲
Jane wants you to create some sort of distraction.
他覺得會讓兇手有膽子溜出去
He thinks it'll encourage him out.
什么樣的插曲啊
What kind of distraction?
別擔心
You know what? Don't worry.
我來搞定
I can handle this.
很好  很好  分頭行動
Great. Great. Let's split up.
"因此人要離開父母
"for this thing shall a man leave his father and mother
與妻子連合
and cleave unto his wife,
二人成為一體"
and the twain shall become one flesh."
聽起來有點亂啊
Whoa. That sounds messy...
但也很美
but beautiful.
謝謝  邦納先生
Thank you, Mr. Bonner.
為我們朗讀稀有又貴重的
Reading from the very rare
《卡佛岱爾圣經》中的內容
and valuable Coverdale Bible.
圣經讀了
Scripture--tick.
戒指  已經交換完了
Rings--we've, uh, we've done that.
你以前干過這事嗎
Have you ever done this before?
你呢
Have you?
當然  我結過婚
Yes. I'm married.
下一步是什么
What's next?
接吻
Kissing.
我也是這么想的
That's what I thought.
如果沒人反對的話
If there are no objections...
沒有
Nope, okay.
根據法律賦予我的權利
By the power vested in me--
通過網絡授予我的圣職
by a mail-order ministry--
我宣布你們正式結為夫妻
I... I now pronounce you husband and wife.
羅伯托
Roberto...
你可以親吻新娘了
you may kiss the bride.
小心保管
Be careful.
可以的話我幫你保管吧
I'll guard that for you, if you'd like.
想得美
You wish.
邦納先生把它交托于我
Mr. Bonner trusted me to lock this away
婚宴時把它鎖到神父的房間里
in the priest's room for the reception, so...
一邊去吧  小子
Step back, son.
抱歉
Excuse me?
謝謝  嘗嘗蛋糕吧
Thank you. Try the cake.
太謝謝了
Oh, thank you.
已經兩個小時了
It's been two hours,
連一個接近出口的人都沒有
and nobody's going anywhere near the exit.
得來點插曲了
We need a distraction.
我看起來怎么樣
Okay. How do I look?
還不錯  怎么了
Fine. Why?
那就好
Good.
抱歉  話筒開著嗎
Excuse me? Is this on?
打擾一下  女士們先生們
Uh, excuse me, ladies and gentlemen,
請給我一點時間說兩句
can I have your attention, for, uh, one second, please?
我還想再給新人送上一段祝酒詞
I'd like to offer one more toast.
我想感謝史黛西和羅伯托
I'd like to thank Stacey and Roberto
讓我明白保護夢想
for making me realize just how important it is
有多么重要
to protect a dream.
我沒有保護好自己的夢想  說實話
I didn't protect my dream. To be honest,
我不知道該怎么做
I, uh, well, I didn't know how.
但是當你在錯誤的時間碰到對的人
But what can you do when you meet the right person
你能怎么辦呢
at the wrong time?
照樣搞她
Do her anyway!
當然這也行
Well, yeah, that works...
可那是暫時的  但是
for a while. But...
最終有些話你說了
Eventually you say things
又或是沒說出口
or don't say things.
犯的錯自己都數不清
You, uh, make more mistakes than you can count.
到了最后
And in the end,
一切分崩離析
things fall apart.
這就是你說的小插曲嗎
Is this your idea of a distraction?
相信我
Trust me.
如果你足夠幸運
Now if you're lucky,
你們也許又會找回彼此
you might find each other again.
但是有太多往事和心痛的事
But there's too much history and heartache
阻擋你回到夢想身邊
to ever find your way back to that dream.
起碼我之前是這么想的
At least that's what I thought.
我希望
I'm hoping...
我想錯了
I was wrong.
格蕾斯
Grace...
你愿意嫁給我嗎
Will you marry me?
說點什么吧  這是真的
Well, say something. This is real.
我愿意  韋恩  我當然愿意嫁給你
Yes, Wayne. Of course I'll marry you.
目標行動了
Target's on the move.
真夠容易的啊
Oh, that was easy.
你怎么知道我會來
How'd you know I'd be here?
在局里吵架的時候
You know, the big fight at the CBI,
只有你希望婚禮
you were the only one that wanted
如期舉行
the wedding to go ahead as planned.
因此  你才是那個有罪的
Ergo, you were the guilty party.
有罪  我只是查看一下圣經
Guilty? I was just checking on the Bible.
我什么都沒做
I didn't do anything.
-你殺了人  -什么
- You killed a man. - What?!
查理別狡辯了  你這是在讓自己難堪
Oh, Charlie, stop. You're just embarrassing yourself.
能用油灰刀撬開門栓的
There's only one way you could jimmy a dead bolt--
方法只有一個
with a putty knife.
你鋸斷了門閂
You sawed through the bolt.
你從派對溜出去
So you snuck out of the party,
但是有人抓了你的現行  對不對
but... somebody caught you in the act, didn't they?
查理
Charlie?
你在這里干什么  拉里
What are you doing here, Larry?
我來偷神父的酒
I came to swipe the priest's wine.
派對的酒喝光了  挺聰明吧
We ran out at the party. Pretty smart, huh?
你在這里干什么
Uh, what are you doing here?
你手里的是鋸嗎
Is that a saw.
你想偷圣經  對不對
You're gonna steal the Bible, aren't you?
你知道這東西的值多少錢嗎
You know how much that thing is worth?
拉里  它上過保險的
Larry, it's insured. All right?
邦納先生會拿到賠款  我們也會發財
Mr. Bonner will get his money, and we'll get rich.
這樣吧  我讓你也入伙
That's right, I'll cut you in.
你這輩子都不用送披薩了
Okay, you'll never have to deliver another pizza in your life.
我其實挺喜歡送披薩的
I kind of like delivering pizzas.
我回派對了
I'm going back to the party now.
拉里  等等
Larry, wait!
你不會告發我吧
Well, you're not gonna tell them, are you?
不會
No, I--
我回去而已  再見
I'm just going back. Bye.
我覺得你不是蓄意要殺他
I don't suppose you wanted to kill him,
不過事與愿違
but, uh, if wishes were horses,
覆水難收
and all that...
你不是本地人
And you not being from around here,
不知道那邊有懸崖
you didn't know about the cliff,
就把尸體丟在池塘里了
so you threw the body in the pond.
你把錢包和能證明身份的東西拿走了
I suppose you took the wallet and I.D.
是想偽裝成搶劫的樣子吧
because you wanted to make it look like a robbery.
把油灰刀放下吧
You can put down the putty knife now.
算了
Whatever.
還是讓我的律師來處理吧  只是
I'll leave this up to my lawyers. Just...
別把手銬銬太緊  行嗎
Don't make the handcuffs too tight, okay?
-銬手銬這事不歸我管  -簡  閃開
- Oh, no, no. I don't do the cuffing... - Jane, move away!
查理  把槍放下
Charlie, put the gun down.
我爸死在了監獄里
My dad died in jail.
我可想呆在外面  勞您費心
I'll take my chances on the outside, thank you.
你現在把我放了
You know, if you just let me go,
事情肯定還有商量的余地
I'm sure they'd be happy to open the dialogue with you.
查理  冷靜
Charlie, stay calm.
你不會想自尋死路的
You don't want to go down this road.
對  你不想的
No, you don't.
都走遠點
Get away from me!
想活命嗎  帶我離開這兒
You wanna live? Get me out of here.
上樓  快  走
Upstairs, now! go!
查理  想想你在做什么
Charlie, think about what you're doing!
-門后是哪里  -不知道
- What's through the door? - No idea.
這兒有我
I'll cover it.
你和瑞斯比  范佩爾去外圍包抄
Set up an exterior perimeter with Rigsby and Van Pelt,
同時呼叫支援
and call for backup.
往前走
Keep moving.
我也想走  查理
Uh, yeah, I'd-- I'd love to, Charlie,
可我沒長翅膀
but without wings--
上屋頂  快
On the roof. Now!
-我們得離開這兒  -好吧
- We're getting out of here. - Okay.
你知道有從這兒下去的路嗎
Uh, you know if there's a-a way down from here?
我們能找到路下去的
We're gonna find a way down.
就怕你這么說
Yeah, that's what I was afraid of.
把槍放下
Drop the gun.
這下他可以見到耶穌本人了
Now he's talking directly to Jesus.
你從哪兒上來的
Where-- where did you come from?
教堂為了修剪樹木架了把伸縮梯
The church keeps an extension ladder for tree trimming.
別往下看  在這兒暈了可不好
Don't look down. Bad place for the spins.
把手給我
Give me your hand.
走吧
Let's go.
你讓我別插手  還好我沒聽你的
Good thing I ignored your request to stay away, huh?
我可能覺得自己有責任照看好你吧
Guess I just felt obliged to keep an eye on you.
是嗎  這話怎么說
Yeah. Why?
事實上  我不信任你
Truth is, I didn't trust ya.
你硬要來插手這個案子
The way you forced your way onto the case here--
我簡直覺得你有什么陰謀
it almost seemed like you had a hidden agenda.
有時候我容易讓人會錯意
Ah, well, sometimes I give out mixed messages.
我這人的眾多缺點之一
It's one of my many failings.
-看來大家都沒事  -當然了
- It looks like everybody's okay? - Sure.
他在那邊屋頂上救了我的命
He saved my life out there on the roof.
應該的
My pleasure.
隨時效勞
I'm at your disposal anytime.
我們樓下見吧
I'll see you two downstairs.
走開  走開
Hey, get it out! get it out!
真沒想到
I didn't see that coming.
最討厭這些東西
I hate those things.
你沒受傷吧
You're not hurt?
我沒事  里斯本
Oh, I'm fine, Lisbon. Ha.
你錯過了好戲  知道嗎
Well, you missed all the action, you know.
是嗎
Oh, I did?
你沒見我在屋頂上的樣子嗎
Did you not see me out there on the roof?
-那才叫好戲呢  -不是這回事
- That was some action. - This is different.
我們可能要比預期
It looks like we're going to be spending
在納帕多呆幾天
a little bit more time in Napa than we expected.
是嗎
Really?
請面對彼此牽手
Join hands and face each other, please.
格蕾斯  你先說
Grace, you'll begin.
跟我重復
Repeat after me.
-我格蕾斯  -我格蕾絲
- I, Grace... - I, Grace...
-愿意你韋恩  -愿意你韋恩
- Take you, Wayne... - Take you, Wayne...
做我的丈夫
to be my husband.
從今往后  相互擁有  相互扶持
To have and to hold from this day forward...
無論是順境或是逆境
For better or for worse,
富有或貧窮
for richer or for poorer,
疾病或健康
in sickness and in health,
彼此相愛相惜
to love and to cherish...
直到死亡將我們分開
until death do us part.
看來你都記熟了
You seem to have that down.
我早就等著這一天了
This has been a long time coming.
輪到你了  韋恩
And now you, Wayne.
就如她剛剛所說的
Uh, everything she just said.
格蕾斯
Grace...
不會再浪費時間了
No more wasted time.
我要和你共度每一天
I want to spend every day with you.
無論未來怎樣
Every day for the rest of our lives
我們將共度余生
and... whatever comes after.
無私的愛沒有起始與終結
Love freely given has no beginning or end.
你們的戒指將代表你們對彼此無止盡的愛
Your rings represent your unending love for each other.
請把格蕾斯的戒指遞給我
May I have the ring for Grace, please?
謝謝
Thanks.
把戒指戴上格蕾斯的手指
Place that ring on Grace's finger
同時請跟我重復
and repeat after me.
這枚戒指代表我對你的愛
I give you this ring as a symbol of my love.
格蕾斯  這枚戒指代表我對你的愛
Grace, I give you this ring as a symbol of my love.
以此戒指為證  我與你締結婚姻
With this ring, I marry you.
With this ring... I marry you.
請把韋恩的戒指遞給我
May we have the ring for Wayne, please?
我想你知道怎么做了吧
I think you know what to do.
是的
Yeah.
韋恩  這枚戒指代表我對你的愛
Wayne, I give you this ring as a symbol of my love.
以此戒指為證  我與你締結婚姻
With this ring, I marry you.
鑒于你們雙方均渴望
Inasmuch as the two of you have made known
并同意結為夫妻
your mutual desire and your consent to be married,
依據我被賦予的權力
by virtue of the authority invested in me,
我宣布你們成為夫妻
I hereby pronounce you husband and wife.
你可以親吻新娘了
You may kiss the bride.
抱歉沒給你想象中的童話般的婚禮
I'm sorry it's not the fairy tale you dreamed of.
只要我愿意  每一天都是童話
I'll take the real thing any day.
二位
Hey, guys...
你們去酒店的馬車備好了
Your ride to the hotel is ready.
還有馬車嗎
We have a ride?
我們有馬車
We have a ride.
21響禮炮  列隊
21-gun salute! Formation!
準備
Ready!
瞄準
Aim!
放
Fire!
我們該出發了
I think that's our cue.
準備
Ready!
瞄準
Aim!
放
Fire!
準備
Ready!
瞄準
Aim!
放
Fire!
新婚